<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="advance">
        <item>Memo</item>
        <item>Personal Information</item>
        <item>Output Result</item>
        <item>Language</item>
        <item>Feedback</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="instructions_main">
        <item>Welcome</item>
        <item>Instructions</item>
        <item>About Snoring</item>
        <item>About Snoring &amp; Diabetes</item>
        <item>FAQs</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="welcome">
        <item>SnoreDiaby</item>
        <item>Place</item>
        <item>Playback</item>
        <item>Intensity</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="snorediaby_cont">
        <item>
            Welcome to SnoreDiaby: the snore recording and sleep tracking app
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="place_cont">
        <item>
            Place your device face down on a table next to your bed with the charger connected.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="playback_cont">
        <item>
            SnoreDiaby shows you when and how loudly you snored and lets you playback audio.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="intensity_cont">
        <item>
            You can test snoring remedies and lifestyle changes to try to reduce your Snore Snore (snoring intensity)
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="instructions">
        <item>Introduction</item>
        <item>Placement</item>
        <item>Results</item>
        <item>Important Disclaimer</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="introduction_cont">
        <item>
            SnoreDiaby is an app that records, measures and tracks your snoring.
            It helps thousands of people just like you to gain insights into their snoring.
            \n\nYou can share SnoreDiaby&#8217;s reports with your doctor or dentist,
            or experiment with snoring remedies and lifestyle changes and track their impact over time.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="placement_cont">
        <item>
            It is recommended placing the device next to your bed with the microphone facing towards you.
            Keep the charger connected if possible to ensure full night monitoring and fully charged device
            the next day.\n\nPlacing the device face down will dim the screen and reduce battery usage.
            \n\nNote: SnoreDiaby is sensitive to ambient noise and works best in quiet environment.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="results_cont">
        <item>
            After each night you&#8217;ll receive a report showing you when and how loudly you snored with
            a selection of audio samples.\n\nYou&#8217;ll also get a Snore Score for the night, which is a
            measure of snoring intensity. If you experiment with snoring remedies or track factors you can
            see how they impact your snoring by the change in your Snore Score.\n\nDon&#8217;t worry too much
            about disk usage, one night of samples only contents 2-4 MB at the default setting.
            You can also delete unwanted sound files and optionally activate full-night recording if you
            want to hear everything.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="important_disclaimer_cont">
        <item>
            SnoreDiaby is not a replacement for a professional sleep study and diagnosis. Snoring can be
            symptomatic of serious sleep disorders (see the section on obstructive sleep apnea below) and you
            should seek immediate medical attention if you are concerned by your symptoms.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="about_snoring">
        <item>What is Snoring?</item>
        <item>Risk Factors</item>
        <item>Obstructive Sleep Apnea</item>
        <item>Snoring Remedies</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="what_cont">
        <item>
            Snoring is noisy breathing whilst you sleep caused by the vibration of soft tissue in your head and neck.
            \n\nThe exact sound you make will depend on the types of soft tissue that is vibrating. For example,
            if the soft tissue at the back of your nose vibrates it is likely you will produce a pinched nasal sound.
            If the tissues at the top of your mouth and the back of your throat vibrate, you will produce a louder, more
            guttural, throaty sound. In most cases, snoring is caused by a combination of areas that are vibrating or blocked.
            \n\nWhile you sleep your airways relax and narrows. This affects air pressure within your airways, which causes
            the tissue to vibrate. This can also happen if your airways are partially blocked, for example if you have a cold.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="risk_cont">
        <item>
            Some things that can increase your risk of habitual snoring include:
            \n\nObesity: particularly if you have a large amount of fat around your neck.
            \n\nAdvancing age: as you get older the muscles tend to weaken, making snoring louder and more prevalent.
            \n\nGenetic factors: some people have a genetic predisposition for snoring due to the structure of their facial anatomy.
            \n\nMouth breathing: drawing in air through your mouth can cause loud snoring as well as dry mouth and bad breath.
            \n\nSeasonal factors: colds, hay fever and low humidity can all impact snoring.
            \n\nAllergic rhinitis: a condition where the inside of your nose becomes swollen and inflamed due to an allergic reaction to substances such as dust or pollen.
            \n\nNasal conditions: nasal polyps and deviated septum can have a major impact on snoring.
            \n\nDrinking alcohol: alcohol relaxes your muscles when you sleep, which increase the narrowing of your airways.
            \n\nSedatives and some types of antidepressants: in some people, these medications can have a similar effect to alcohol on the muscles.
            \n\nSmoking: tobacco smoke can cause your airways to become inflamed, which increases the narrowing of the airways.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="obstructive_cont">
        <item>
            Obstructive sleep apnea (OSA) is a condition where the walls of the throat relax and narrow during sleep, interrupting normal breathing.
            \n\nBreathing is totally or partially interrupted for periods of 10 seconds or more, typically followed by a choking or gasping sound.
            \n\nOSA has a high prevalence and is frequently undiagnosed.
            \n\nSymptoms of OSA include:
            \n\n&#183; Loud snoring
            \n&#183; Noisy and laboured breathing
            \n&#183; Repeated short periods where breathing is interrupted
            \n&#183; Not feeling refreshed after waking up
            \n&#183; Feeling very sleepy during the day
            \n&#183; Poor memory and concentration
            \n&#183; Night sweats
            \n&#183; Frequently waking up during the night to urinate
            \n&#183; Headaches, particularly in the morning
            \n&#183; Irritability and mood swings
            \n&#183; Depression
            \n&#183; Loss of libido
            \n\nObstructive sleep apnea can have very serious consequences if left untreated.
            \n\nIf you are concerned by your symptoms you should make a full night recording of your snoring with SnoreLab and speak to your doctor.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="remedies_cont">
        <item>
            As there are so many possible causes of snoring there is no one snoring remedy that works for everyone. You may need to try a few before you discover one that works for you.
            \n\nThe most successful remedies amongst SnoreLab users include:
            \n\nCPAP: CPAP is the outstanding treatment option for people with obstructive sleep apnea. The user wears a mask connected to a machine that creates positive airway pressure to prevent airway collapse. Take your SnoreLab recordings to your doctor to learn more. (Full night recording is recommended)
            \n\nMouthpieces: anti-snoring dental appliances typically work by advancing the lower jaw by a few millimeters to reduce airway blockage. Cheap mouthpieces available online can be very effective but for superior comfort you may choose to invest in a custom fitted mouthpiece, which are supplied by dentists. Take your SnoreLab recordings to your dentist to learn more. (Full night recording is recommended)
            \n\nTheravent: a special plaster that covers your nostrils to create positive pressure in your airways. Theravent works like a milder form of CPAP using the power of your own breathing rather than a machine.
            \n\nAir purifiers: if your snoring sounds nasal, you may well benefit from an air purifier to remove dust and allergens from the air.
            \n\nNasal products: if you snore more when your nose is blocked, you can try products that reduce nasal congestion such as neti pot, nasal strips or a nasal dilator.
            \n\nSide sleeping: side sleeping can be effective when snoring is triggered by compression of the throat. Putting a pillow between your legs can make side sleeping more comfortable.
            \n\nWeight loss: being overweight is one of the most common causes of snoring. You can use SnoreLab to track your weight over time to compare against your snoring.
            \n\nLifestyle changes: lifestyle factors such as drinking alcohol can have a major impact your snoring. SnoreLab is designed to measure their impact, which may encourage you to make changes.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="about_diabetes">
        <item>What is Type 2 Diabetes?</item>
        <item>Sleep &amp; Type 2 Diabetes</item>
        <item>How To Improve It?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="what_t2d">
        <item>什麼是第二型糖尿病？</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sleep_t2d">
        <item>睡眠與糖尿病的關係</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="advice_t2d">
        <item>如何改善</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="faqs">
        <item>Device Positioning</item>
        <item>Disk Usage</item>
        <item>Exporting Sound Files</item>
        <item>Two Snorers in the Room</item>
        <item>About SnoreDiaby</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="device_cont">
        <item>
            SnoreDiaby is sensitive to device placement and will tend to give louder readings when the device
            is closer to the snorer. We recommend placing the device on a nightstand next to the bed with the
            microphone facing the snorer. If this is not possible the phone can be placed on the bed. If you
            use the app to compare your snoring between nights you should always position the device in the
            same position to give consistent readings.
            \n\nAlthough we advise you to keep the device connected to the charger this is not strictly necessary
            if the device is well charged.
            \n\nSnoreDiaby can run successfully with the device locked but this may lead the recording being
            terminated by interruptions. SnoreLab will automatically prevent the device from locking unless you
            press the power button, close your iPad cover, or exit the app. On older iOS devices, the phone may
            lock automatically to minimize other activity on the phone.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="disk_cont">
        <item>
            In its default setting SnoreLab uses 2-4 MB a night. If you activate full night recording, one night
            of samples typically uses 64-128 MB. The recordings are divided into short samples allowing you to
            mark individual samples as favorites and delete the rest.
            \n\nYou can delete old or unwanted recordings in several ways:
            \n\nIndividual nights: to access the &#8217;delete audio&#8217; option press the &#8217;dots&#8217;
            button on the Snore Report or the &#8217;bin&#8217; button on the calendar page. To prevent individual
            samples from being deleted, mark them with a &#8217;star&#8217; when playing the sample.
            \n\nBulk deletion: the Audio Archive function in the menu is designed to quickly free disk space by
            deleting old audio recordings. You can specify the number of recordings that you&#8217;d like to be
            retained for historic records (or none at all) and the rest will be deleted. Recordings marked with a
            star will not be deleted.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="exporting_cont">
        <item>
            If you would like to email audio files you can use the &#8217;share&#8217; button in the top right of
            the Snore Report. To manually select audio files press the &#8217;paperclip&#8217; button when playing a sample.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="snorers_cont">
        <item>
            SnoreDiaby cannot automatically distinguish one person&#8217;s snoring from another&#8217;s.
            \n\nIf you want to see who is the worst snorer we suggest that you run the app a few
            times with only one person in the room and make a note of this using a custom factor
            within the Factors menu e.g. &#8217;Steve&#8217;.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="about_cont">
        <item>
            SnoreDiaby was created by a husband after his wife complained about his snoring.
            \n\nIf you enjoy or benefit from SnoreDiaby please do leave a review in the App Store
            and talk about it amongst your family and friends.
            \n\nWe wish you success in your journey!
            \n\nwww.snorediaby.com
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="null_cont">
        <item>Null</item>
    </string-array>







    <string-array name="items_array_expandable_level_one">
        <item>Level 1.1</item>
        <item>Level 1.2</item>
        <item>Level 1.3</item>
        <item>Level 1.4</item>
        <item>Level 1.5</item>
        <item>Level 1.6</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="items_array_expandable_level_one_one_child">
        <item>Level 1.1.1</item>
        <item>Level 1.1.2</item>
        <item>Level 1.1.3</item>
        <item>Level 1.1.4</item>
        <item>Level 1.1.5</item>
        <item>Level 1.1.6</item>
        <item>Level 1.1.7</item>
        <item>Level 1.1.8</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="items_array_expandable_level_one_two_child">
        <item>Level 1.2.1</item>
        <item>Level 1.2.2</item>
        <item>Level 1.2.3</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="items_array_expandable_level_two">
        <item>Second Level 01</item>
        <item>Second Level 02</item>
        <item>Second Level 03</item>
        <item>Second Level 04</item>
        <item>Second Level 05</item>
        <item>Second Level 06</item>
        <item>Second Level 07</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="items_array_expandable_level_three">
        <item>Third Level 01</item>
        <item>Third Level 02</item>
        <item>Third Level 03</item>
        <item>Third Level 04</item>
        <item>Third Level 05</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>

